

Santiago Jose Oviedo Gonzalez

Date of birth: 23/03/1994 **Nationality:** Colombian

CONTACT



47 Gejza Street,, Flat 1 Swieqi, Malta (Home)



santiago24612@gmail.com



(+356) 79394418

ABOUT ME

Customer service expert with more than four years of work experience in contact centers. Expert at managing 80+ calls each day while resolving client issues efficiently and effectively. I'm fluent in English and Spanish, and I am able to provide straightforward customer assistance in both languages.

WORK EXPERIENCE

15/10/2016 - 11/05/2019 Medellin, Colombia

Call center representative Teleperformance

- Devoted special emphasis to punctuality and worked to maintain outstanding attendance record, timeously arriving at work ready to start immediately
- Worked with different customers to understand requirements and provide exceptional customer service

04/11/2019 - 24/01/2022 Medellin, Colombia

Customer service representative Stanley Black and Decker

- Resolved 300+ weekly customer inquiries via phone and email, consistently exceeding targets
- Tracked trends in customers feedback and collaborated with management to determine the root cause of issues

29/08/2022 - CURRENT Swatar, Malta

Contact centre generalist HSBC

- · Assist with accounts on balance, make transfers account to account, transfer customers to other departments, notate accounts, troubleshooting debit cards, update profiles and in transactions.
- · Help with card services and customer facing technologies such as online banking, mobile banking, and telephone banking.
- · Research and resolve issues in a friendly and timely manner

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

22/01/2011 - 04/12/2013 Monteria, Colombia

Chef Gastronomy diploma

Address Cra. 6 #33-02, , Monteria, Colombia

15/01/2005 - 01/10/2010 Montería, Colombia

High school diploma Academia Gustavo Rojas Pinilla

Address Cra. 8 #33-53, Montería, Colombia

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Spanish

Other language(s):

English

Listening	Reading	Spoken	Spoken	Writing
C1	C1	production	interaction	C1
		B2	C1	

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Word | Microsoft Excel | Facebook | Social Media Zoom Outlook | Google Drive | Instagram | LinkedIn | Google Docs | Sa les Force Zendesk